AKONI OLUWADAMILOLA NOUAH

Software Engineer

08153579979

Email: noahgreatakoni@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/Greatnex1

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nouah-great-449438168/

Portfolio: https://github.com/Greatnex1/myportfolio

SUMMARY

I'm a software engineer with about three years of experience from Nigeria. I strive to efficiently utilize my proficient problem-solving abilities and diverse experience in different technologies to contribute dynamic ideas in software development. Am committed to creating with Confidence a more viable product that will change our world.

Experience

March 2022 - Present

Semicolon Africa, Lagos - Software Engineer

- ❖ Learned the adoption of software development life-cycle principles for software applications that meet industry standards.
- ❖ Developed APIs ranging from an E-commerce platform, Blog web pages, systems, and Banking web

application, using Java and Spring-boot.

♦ Designed and implemented Entity Relational Diagrams.

August 2020 - October 2021

Design-Loft Nigeria Limited, Lagos - Front End Web Developer Intern

Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement.

and translated user requirements into project designs and

implementation plans, created site layout and user interface using HTML and CSS practices.

EDUCATION:

University Of Benin, Nigeria - B.sc(Edu)

2016-2021

Education and Biology

SKILLS:

Fluent: Javascript, Java, UML, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Html, CSS, Python

Advanced: React, Nodejs

Intermediate: Typescript, GO

PROJECTS

Title: An E-commerce System

Github: https://github.com/Greatnex1/lum-express

Title: A Musical Website

GitHub: https://github.com/Greatnex1/web-dev

Title: A Quiz loop

Github: https://github.com/Greatnex1/quiz